created_by: mmurphy
task_description: 'Use the NATO Phonetic alphabet'
seed_examples:
- answer: 'romeo, echo, delta, hotel, alpha,tango'
  question: 'Spell ''redhat'' using the nato phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Sierra, Papa, Echo, Lima, Lima'
  question: 'Spell ''spell'' using the nato phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'tango-hotel-echo quebec-uniform-india-charlie-kilo
           bravo-romeo-oscar-whiskey-november foxtrot-oscar-xray'
  question: 'Spell ''The quick brown fox'' using the nato phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'juliett-uniform-mike-papa-sierra oscar-victor-echo-romeo tango-hotel-echo
           lima-alpha-zulu-yankee delta-oscar-golf-sierra'
  question: 'Spell ''jumps over the lazy dogs'' using the nato phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Alpha, November, Sierra, Whiskey, Echo, Romeo'
  question: 'Spell ''answer'' using the nato phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Quebec, Uniform, Echo, Sierra, Tango, India, Oscar, November'
  question: 'Spell ''question'' using the nato phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'oscar-papa-echo-november sierra-oscar-uniform-romeo-charlie-echo'
  question: 'using the Nato phonetic alphabet spell ''open source'''
- answer: 'If someone is having a problem understanding a particular word,
           you can spell it out using the NATO phonetic alphabet, which is widely used in radio communications.
           To indicate that you are about to spell the word, it''s normally preceeded by the phrase ''I spell'',
           for example, to spell the would ''phonetic'' you could say
           ''I spell papa-hotel-oscar-november-echo-tango-india-charlie'''
  question: 'how do you talk over a radio link where the other person cannot understand a word due to poor connection'
- answer: 'The Nato phonetic alphabet is use to aid in the clear reception of information over poor radio
           communication links,
           where each letter is replaced by a particular word,
           The alphapet "ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ" is replaced by the words
           "Alpha-Bravo-Charlie-Delta-Echo-Foxtrot-Golf-Hotel-India-Juliett-Kilo-Lima-Mike-
           November-Oscar-Papa-Quebec-Romeo-Sierra-Tango-Uniform-Victor-Whiskey-Xray-Yankee-Zulu"
           for example the word "what" is replaced with "whiskey-hotel-alpha-tango"'
  question: 'what is the Nato phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Golf, Alpha, Tango, Echo, Kilo, Echo, Echo, Papa, Echo, Romeo'
  question: 'Spell ''gatekeeper'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Alpha, Tango, Romeo, Oscar, Papa, India, Delta, Alpha, Echo'
  question: 'Spell ''Atropidae'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Sierra, Hotel, Alpha, Charlie, Kilo, Lima, Echo, Whiskey, India, Sierra, Echo'
  question: 'Spell ''shacklewise'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Alpha, Romeo, Charlie, Hotel, India, Bravo, Echo, November, Tango, Hotel, Oscar, Sierra'
  question: 'Spell ''archibenthos'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Mike, Oscar, Romeo, Alpha, Charlie, Echo, Oscar, Uniform, Sierra'
  question: 'Spell ''moraceous'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Sierra, Tango, Alpha, Tango, Echo, Foxtrot, Uniform, Lima'
  question: 'Spell ''stateful'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Whiskey, India, Sierra, Hotel, Mike, Alpha, Yankee'
  question: 'Spell ''wishmay'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Foxtrot, Lima, Oscar, Oscar, Romeo, Echo, Romeo'
  question: 'Spell ''floorer'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Charlie, Oscar, Uniform, November, Tango, Echo, Romeo, Tango, Romeo, Alpha, Victor, Echo, Romeo,
           Sierra, Echo'
  question: 'Spell ''countertraverse'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Uniform, November, Charlie, Romeo, Alpha, Victor, India, November, Golf, Lima, Yankee'
  question: 'Spell ''uncravingly'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Echo, Charlie, Hotel, India, November, Oscar, Sierra, Papa, Hotel, Alpha, Echo, Romeo, India, Tango,
           Echo, Sierra'
  question: 'Spell ''Echinosphaerites'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Bravo, Oscar, Romeo, Alpha, Charlie, India, Foxtrot, Echo, Romeo, Oscar, Uniform, Sierra'
  question: 'Spell ''boraciferous'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Mike, Oscar, Romeo, India, November, Golf, Alpha, Delta'
  question: 'Spell ''moringad'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Charlie, Oscar, November, Foxtrot, India, Delta, Echo, Romeo'
  question: 'Spell ''confider'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Sierra, Uniform, Papa, Echo, Romeo, Charlie, Oscar, Oscar, Lima'
  question: 'Spell ''supercool'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Bravo, Oscar, Tango, Uniform, Lima, India, November, Uniform, Mike'
  question: 'Spell ''botulinum'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Charlie, Alpha, Lima, Lima, India, Golf, Romeo, Alpha, Papa, Hotel, Echo, Romeo'
  question: 'Spell ''calligrapher'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Papa, Romeo, Echo, Sierra, India, Golf, November'
  question: 'Spell ''presign'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Romeo, Echo, Victor, India, Sierra, Echo, Romeo'
  question: 'Spell ''reviser'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Papa, Alpha, Romeo, Alpha, Mike, Echo, Tango, Romeo, India, Tango, India, Charlie'
  question: 'Spell ''parametritic'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Bravo, Uniform, Tango, Yankee, Lima, India, Charlie'
  question: 'Spell ''butylic'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Mike, Yankee, Tango, Hotel, Oscar, Mike, Alpha, November, India, Alpha'
  question: 'Spell ''mythomania'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Papa, India, Sierra, Tango, Oscar, Lima, Golf, Romeo, Alpha, Mike'
  question: 'Spell ''pistolgram'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Sierra, Alpha, Romeo, Papa, Oscar'
  question: 'Spell ''sarpo'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'
- answer: 'Charlie, Alpha, November, Tango, Hotel, Alpha, Romeo, India, Delta, India, Alpha, November'
  question: 'Spell ''cantharidian'' using the NATO phonetic alphabet'


